Erwin Panofsky
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1921-1978, undated, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-16; 16 linear ft. Reels 2108-2128)
  - Colleagues, Scholars, Students and Other Individuals, 1921-1978, undated, 1.1:
    - Dienstfrey - Dobrzeniecki, 1938-1968 (Box 3, Reel 2111)
      Dienstfrey, Debra
      Dinsmoor, William B.
      Dobrzeniecki, Tadeusz
    - Dodd - Downey, 1931-1965 (Box 3, Reel 2111-2112)
      Dodd, Lamar
      Dodgson, Campbell
      Dodwell, Charles Reginald
      Dohmann, Albrecht
      Donati, Lamberto
    - Drake, Stillman, 1955-1968 (Box 3, Reel 2111-2112)
    - Dupont, Jacques, 1952-1963, undated (Box 3, Reel 2111-2112)
    - Dussler, Luitpold, 1964-1971 (Box 3, Reel 2111-2112)
    - E, General (single letters, Eakins - Escala), 1937-1966 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
      Eakins, J. M.
      Earle, Edward Mead
      Edgar, Esabella M.
      Edgar, Sister Mary
      Edgerton
      Edwards, Audrey L.
      Egri
      Ehrman, A.
      Eichenberg, Fritz
      Einstein, Alfred
      Einstein, Norbert
      Eismann, Heinrich
      Eisenberg, Marvin
      Eliasberg, Wladimir G.
      Ellis, Albert
      Emboden, William Al
      Emerson, William
      Emmens, J. A.
      Engelbregt, Father J.H.A.
      Engleson, H.
      Epstein, Marion K.
      Erdberg, Joan Prentice von
      Er-Shih, Chiang
      Erlebacher, Walter
      Erler, Adalbert
      Erskine, Peggy A.
      Escala, Donna N.
    - Ebbingewubben, J. C., 1951-1963 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Edelstein, Ludwig and Renate, 1952-1965 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Eerden - Egan, 1947-1952 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
      Eerden, J. H. van der
      Egan, Patricia
    - Egbert, Donald Drew and Virginia Wylie, 1941-1967 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - de Egrey, Anne, 1956-1964 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Einem, Herbert von, 1953-1967 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Einstein, Albert and Margot, 1938-1964 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Eisenhart, Luther P., 1949-1956 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Eisler, Colin, 1951-1965 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Eissler, K. R., 1957-1960 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Ellenius, Allen, 1957-1968 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Engels - Epstein, 1937-1967 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
      Engels, J.
      Engler, Gustav Andreas
      English, Anne Whitall
      Epstein, Fritz T.
    - Erffa, Hans Martin Feiherr von, 1956-1962 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Erffa, Helmut Freiherr von, 1940-1967 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Esmerian - Ettinghausen, 1942-1967 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
      Esmerian, Ralph O.
      Ettinghausen, Richard
    - Ettlinger, Leopold D., 1953-1967 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Euler, Walter, 1958 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - F, General (single letters, Fagles - Furniss), 1931-1967, (2 folders) (Box 4, Reel 2112)
      Fagles, Robert
      Fait, Joachim
      Falkenstein, Henry
      Färber, Helmut
      Fee, James Alger
      Feifel, Herman
      Feltenstein, Rosalie
      Ferguson, Wallace K.
      Fergusson, Francis
      Ferrara, Luisa Balboni-Sindaco di
      Ferrari, Angel
      Ferrari, Guy
      Feron, Madame Raymonde
      Field Enterprises, Inc.
      Filia, Joan
      Filipetto, Gino
      Film, Carin
      Finch, Henry A.
      Fingesten, Peter
      Fink, June-Marie
      Finlayson, Donald L.
      Fischer, L.
      Flagg, Richard B.
      Fleming, John F.
      Fleming, John V.
      Flexner, Abrahae
      Flitner, Wilhelm
      Foelsch
      Folliet, G.
      Foltiny, Stephen
      Forbes, J. D.
      Forbes, Kenneth Ripley
      Foreman, Clark
      Forslund, Erik
      Forth, Robert F.
      Foster, Philip
      Foster, Sharon
      Fowle, J. W.
      Fowler, George
      Fowles, Jean
      Fox, John
      Fox, Milton S.
      Fraenkel, Hans
      Francia, P. L. de
      Francis, William
      Frankena, William
      Frantz, Sally
      Fraser, Russell A.
      Freccero, John
      Freimarck, Vincent
      French and Company, Inc.
      Frenkel, Thomas
      Frey, Dagobert
      Friberg, Axel
      Fried, Alexander
      Friedenwald, Jonas S.
      Fritz, Rolf
      Fröbe-Kapteyn, Olga
      Fulton, John
      Furnies
      Furniss, W. Todd
    - Faglio-dell A'Rco - Federer, 1952-1967 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
      Fagiolo-dell A'Rco, Maurizio and Marcello
      Faison, S. Lane, Jr.
      Federer, Georg
    - Fehl, Philipp, 1955-1967 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Fenyö, Iván, 1960-1965 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Ferguson, Wallace K., 1953-1965 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Fernández, Justino, 1961-1964 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Ferry, W. H., 1962-1965 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Fierz, Marcus, 1955-1964 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Finkelstein - Fisher, 1953-1967 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
      Finkelstein, Louis
      Fiocco, Giuseppe
      Fisher, Martha
    - Fitchen, John F., 1955-1956 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Fogg, John M., Jr., 1951-1952 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Folie, Jacqueline, 1954-1967 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Fong, Wen, 1955-1963 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Fontaine - Forssman, 1954-1966 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
      Fontaine, Mrs. F. D.
      Ford Foundation
      Forssman, Erik
    - Forsyth, George H., Jr., 1946-1965, undated (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Forsyth - Foster, 1951-1966 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
      Forsyth, William H.
      Fosdick, Sina
      Foster, Charles A.
    - Franc, Helen M., 1950-1966 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Francastle - Fränkel, 1946-1959 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
      Francastel, Pierre
      Fränkel, Hermann
    - Frankel - Frankfort, 1951-1964 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
      Frankel, Walter K.
      Frankfort, Henri
    - Frankl, Paul, 1939-1961 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
    - Frantz - Frenken, 1951-1966 (Box 4, Reel 2112)
      Frantz, Alison
      Freedberg, Sydney
      Frenken, T.W.M.
    - Freudenheim - Friedländer, 1933-1965 (Box 4, Reel 2113)
      Freudenheim, Tom L.
      Freyhan, R.
      Friedländer, Max J.
      Friedländer, Paul
    - Friedländer, Walter, 1932-1966, (2 folders) (Box 4, Reel 2113)
    - Friedman, 1936-1955 (Box 4, Reel 2113)
      Friedman, Lionel J.
      Friedman, William F.
    - Friedmann, Herbert, 1945-1966 (Box 4, Reel 2113)
    - Friend - Fulton, 1952-1961 (Box 4, Reel 2113)
      Friend, Albert H., Jr.
      Fritz, Kurt von
      Fulton, John F.
    - Gallenkamp - Gutkind (single letters), 1942-1968 (Box 4, Reel 2113)
      Gallenkamp, George V.
      Garbee, Willialm C., Jr.
      Gardie, Krinstina de la
      Garrett, Robert
      Garttmer, Lloyd
      Gellerman, Hersh
      Gellert, Bridget
      Gendler, Rabbi Everett
      Gibson, James J.
      Gilbert, Marianne
      Gilbert, Mary E.
      Gilbert, Philip
      Gilbert, William
      Gillispie, Charles C.
      Gillmer, Vaun
      Gilmore, Gerald F.
      Gilmore, Myron F.
      Ginzburg, Carlo
      Glasser, Hannelore
      Glazier, William S.
      Goldenberg, Anne
      Goldschmidt, Lucien
      Goldstein, C.
      Gonzalez, Joaquin Diaz
      Goris, Jan-Albert
      Gova, Sabine
      Goodall, Donald
      Gottlieb, Carla
      Gottschalk, Louis
      Graubard, Stephen R.
      Graupe, Paul
      Green, P. Charles
      Greenberg, Sidney
      Greenbie, Sydney
      Greene, J. Craig
      Greene, Terrence W.
      Griffin, Gillett
      Griffing, Robert P.
      Griffith, Beatrice Fox
      Grun, Edith
      Guillevic, J.
      Gulamerian, Norman B.
      Gutkind, E. A.
    - Gabriel, Father A. L., 1949-1962 (Box 4, Reel 2113)
    - Gagnebin-Ganter, 1957-1967 (Box 4, Reel 2113)
      Gagnebin, Bernard
      Galpin, Perrin C.
      Ganter, Joseph
    - Garbáty, 1949-1959 (Box 4, Reel 2113)
      Garbáty, Eugene Leopold
      Garbáty, Maurice
    - Gareis - Garside, 1953-1965 (Box 4, Reel 2113)
      Gareis, Hansgeorg
      Garside, Charles, Jr.
    - Gäumann-Wild - Gauthier, 1956-1966 (Box 5, Reel 2113)
      Gäumann-Wild, Doris
      Gauthier, Marie-Madeline
    - Gelder, Jan G. van, 1951-1967, (2 folders) (Box 5, Reel 2113)
    - Gerson, Horst, 1946-1966 (Box 5, Reel 2113)
    - Gessner, Robert, 1948-1961, undated (Box 5, Reel 2113)
    - Geyl - Giesau, 1924-1968 (Box 5, Reel 2113)
      Geyl, Pieter
      Gibbons, Felton
      Giesau, Hermann
    - Giesey, Ralph E., 1953-1966, undated (Box 5, Reel 2113)
    - Gilbert, Creighton, 1948-1965 (Box 5, Reel 2113)
    - Gilbert - Godwin, 1942-1966 (Box 5, Reel 2113)
      Gilbert, Felix
      Gnudi, Cesare
      Godwin, Frances Gray
    - Goetz, Oswald, 1950-1953 (Box 5, Reel 2113)
    - Goldberg - Goldman, 1947-1963, undated (Box 5, Reel 2113)
      Goldberg, Milton
      Goldberg, Norman L.
      Goldman, Hetty
    - Goldschmidt, Adolph, 1924-1970 (Box 5, Reel 2113)
    - Goldschmidt - Goldwater, 1936-1960 (Box 5, Reel 2113)
      Goldschmidt, Max
      Goldwater, Robert
    - Gombrich, Ernst H., 1946-1967 (Box 5, Reel 2113)
    - Goodchild - Gordon, 1941-1960 (Box 5, Reel 2113)
      Goodchild, Donald
      Goodenough, Erwin R.
      Goodnell, Robert C.
      Gordon, Irene
    - Goris - Gould, 1947-1960 (Box 5, Reel 2113)
      Goris, Jan Albert
      Gosebruch, Martin
      Gottesman, D. S. (D.S. and R.H. Gottesman Foundation)
      Gould, Cecil
    - Graaf - Grange, 1929-1964 (Box 5, Reel 2113)
      Graaf, J. A. van de
      Gradenwitz
      Grange, T. P.
    - Green, Rosalie B., 1954-1967, undated (Box 5, Reel 2113)
    - Greenbaum - Greene, 1940-1970 (Box 5, Reel 2113)
      Greenbaum, Edward E.
      Greene, Belle da Costa
    - Greenhaus, Carla, 1962-1965 (Box 5, Reel 2113)
    - Greischel - Griffith, 1956-1965 (Box 5, Reel 2113)
      Greischel, Walther
      Grier, Harry
      Griffith, Charles Francis
      Griffith, Richard
    - Grinten, E. F. van der, 1953-1965 (Box 5, Reel 2113)
    - Grippi, Rosalind, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Reel 2114)
    - Grodecki, Louis, 1948-1967, undated (Box 5, Reel 2114)
    - Grosjean - Grote, 1946-1966 (Box 5, Reel 2114)
      Grosjean, Paul
      Grossman, Edwin
      Grote, Ludwig
    - Guldan, Ernst, 1967-1971 (Box 5, Reel 2114)
    - Grenebaum - Guerry, 1948-1967 (Box 5, Reel 2114)
      Grenebaum, L. H.
      de Gruyter, Walter
      Guenther, Peter W.
      Guerlac, Henry
      Guerry, Prosper
    - Gulden - Gwaltney, 1940-1971 (Box 5, Reel 2114)
      Gulden, Ernst
      Gundersheimer, H.
      Gurewich, Vladimir
      Gutiérrez Mujica, Carlos
      Gutmann, Joseph
      Gwaltney, Corbin
    - H, General (single letters, Hackenbroch - Huth), 1937-1967, (2 folders) (Box 5, Reel 2114)
      Hackenbroch, Yvonne
      Hadassah Magazine
      Haering, Irene
      Halberstam, Michael J.
      Halle, Kay
      Hallowell, Robert E.
      Hamberg, Gustav
      Hamburger Frendenblatt
      Hamilton, Thomas H.
      Hanfstaengl, Eberhard
      Harbiso, E. Harris
      Madelean Harmann
      Harrison, Evelyn B.
      Harrison, Frank L.
      Harrsen, Meta
      ???tHart, M. E.
      Hartman, Otto
      Harvey, E. Newton
      Harvey, Marlene
      Harwi, Lawrence
      Häskum, Richard
      Hauben, Janet
      Haufrecht, Betty
      Haugen, Pat
      Haupt, Hans
      Hausmann, U.
      Havenitt, Elaine
      Haverlin, Carl
      Hayek, F. A. von
      Healy, Arthur K. D.
      Hedén, Karl-Gusstaf
      Heemstra, Baron F.S. Sixma van
      Heger, Henrik
      Heidegger
      Heijmans, Eduard
      Heilbrunn, Rudolf M.
      Heinemann, F.
      Heinemann, Rudolf J.
      Heinrich, Ted
      Heisenberg, Werner
      Held, Richard
      Helleiner, Karl T.
      Henderson, George
      Henry, Father Paul
      Herbig, Reinhard
      Herlig,
      Herding, Klaus
      Hernmarck, Carl
      Herring, James V.
      Hersey, Carl K.
      Heyl, Lawrence
      Heymann, Frederick G.
      HiFi/Stereo Review
      Hilweg, Hans
      Hind'Hulsh, R.
      Hinman, Richard L.
      Hirsch, Stefan
      Hoening, Irene
      Hoffeld, Jeffrey M.
      Hoffmann, Konrad
      Hofstede, Justus Müller
      Hohenzollern, Prinz Johann Georg von
      Holborn, Hajo
      Holmqvist, Wilhelm
      Hook, Sidney
      Hootz
      Hopper, Paul
      Horen
      Horizon
      Hoving, Walter
      Howell, Douglass
      Howell, E. B.
      Howell, Warren R.
      Hughes, Serge
      Hugo, Harold
      Humez
      Hupert, Marjorie
      Hürlimann, Caspar G.
      Hürlimann, Hans
      Hurt, Hethro M., III
      Huth, Hans
    - Hahnloser - Hamilton, 1950-1966 (Box 5, Reel 2114)
      Hahnloser, Hans R.
      Haight, Anne
      Haight, Elizabeth Hazelton
      Hamberg, Gustaf
      Hamilton, George Heard
    - Hammer, Victor, 1946-1978 (Box 5, Reel 2114)
    - Hampe - Hanson, 1948-1964 (Box 5, Reel 2114)
      Hampe, Roland
      Hanckel, Hadumoth
      Hanson, Bernard
      Hanson, Norwood R.
    - Harbison, 1944-1967 (Box 5, Reel 2114)
      Harbison, Craig S.
      Harbison, E. Harris
    - Harris - Hartmann, 1951-1965 (Box 5, Reel 2114)
      Harris, Robert M.
      Hartmann, Kurt
    - Hartt, Frederick, 1938-1964 (Box 5, Reel 2114)
    - Hatch - Heath, 1956-1966 (Box 5, Reel 2114)
      Hatch, John Davis
      Hatzfeld, Helmut
      Haussherr, Reiner
      Haycraft, Robert K.
      Heath, William W.
    - Heckscher, William S., 1945-1967, (5 folders) (Box 5, Reel 2114)
    - Hermann, Adelheid, 1937-1967 (Box 6, Reel 2114)
    - Heiss - Heitmann, 1931-1968 (Box 6, Reel 2114)
      Heiss, Carl Georg
      Heitmann, Klaus
    - Held, Julius S., 1948-1967 (Box 6, Reel 2114)
    - Helsdingen - Hess, 1938-1968 (Box 6, Reel 2114)
      Helsdingen, H. W. van
      Hempel, Eberhard
      Henle, Werner
      Henry, Barklie McKee
      Hentzen, A.
      Hermerén, Göran, undated
      Herrlinger, Robert
      Hertz, Richard
      Hess, Jacob
    - Heydenreich, Ludwig H., 1949-1967, undated, (2 folders) (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
    - Heyl - Hinks, 1951-1965 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
      Heyl, Bernard C.
      Hibbard, Howard
      Hinks, Roger
    - Hirschfeld, Peter, 1937-1972 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
    - Hirtum - Hochschild, 1937-1972 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
      Hirtum, Andrée van
      Hitchcock, Henry-Russell
      Hochschild, Mrs. Harold K.
    - Hofer, Phil, 1946-1966 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
    - Hoff - Hoffmann, 1952-1967 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
      Hoff, Ursula
      Hoffmann, Kathrin
    - Hollander - Holt, 1953-1967 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
      Hollander, John
      Hollister, C. Warren
      Holmback, A.
      Holst, Christian von
      Holt, Mrs. John B.
    - Holzinger - Hope, 1949-1972 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
      Holzinger, Ernst
      Hoogewerff, G. J.
      Hope, Henry
    - Horb - Horn, 1948-1965 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
      Horb, Felix
      Horn, Walter W.
    - Hornung - Hubala, 1950-1967 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
      Hornung, Hans
      Horváth, Béla
      Houtzager, Maria Elisabeth
      Hubala, Erich
    - d'Hulst, R. A., 1954-1962 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
    - Hungerland - Iklé, 1946-1961 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
      Hungerland, Helmut
      Hunt, F. L.
      Iklé, Charles F.
    - Ionescu, Theodor, 1958-1968 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
    - Isserstedt - Ivins, 1955-1965 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
    - Isserstedt, Dorothea C., 1955 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
    - Ivanoff, Nicolas, 1961-1965 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
    - Iversen, Erik, 1955-1961 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
    - Ivins, William M., Jr., 1955 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
    - J, General (single letters, Jacobs - Jung), 1946-1967 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
      Jacobs, Lewis
      Jacobsen, Eric
      Jacquot, Jean
      Jahn, Erich
      Jakobson, Roman
      James, C.L.R.
      Janicik, Edward E. C.
      Janson, Bertil
      Janson, Claire
      Jastrow, Elizabeth
      Jauneau, MaadeleineRocher
      Jauss
      Javet, Pierre
      Jesi, Furio
      Jirat-Wasiutynski, Vojt ch
      John, James J.
      Johnson, Edgar N.
      Johnson, Philip C.
      de Jong, Mrs. H.M.E.
      Jost, Res
      Jung, Eva-Marie
    - James - Jameson, 1954-1956 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
      James, David
      Jaffé, Michael
      James, Mr. and Mrs. William
      Jameson, D.F.B.
    - Janson, H. W., 1936-1967, (3 folders) (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
    - Jessen - Johnson, 1948-1968 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
      Jessen, H.
      Johnson, James R.
      Johnson, Lee
      Johnson, S. F.
      Johnson, W. McAllister
    - Jones - Jurgen, 1950-1968 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
      Jones, Bob, Jr.
      Jones, Eldred D.
      Josephson, Ragnar
      Jucker, Hans
      Jurgen, Paul
    - K, General (single letters, Kahler - Kuylen), 1948-1967 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
      Kahler, Erich
      Kaizer, Joachim
      Kallen, Horace M. Peter Kamp, van de
      Katona, Paul
      Kaysen, Carl
      Kearns, Helen M.
      Keeper of the King's Pictures
      Keil, Robert A.
      Kellogg, Alfred L.
      Kelly, Leon
      Kennick, William E.
      Kerby-Miller, Charles
      Kern, Paul J.
      Kernodle, George R.
      Kielland, Else Christie
      Kieser, Emil
      Killermann, Sebastian
      Klein, Jerome
      Klimowsky, E. W.
      Knauer, G. Nicholas
      Knipping, J. B.
      Knowlton, Edgar C.
      Knuttel, G.
      Koch, Karl
      Koher, Harris
      Kolb, Albert
      Koslow, Arnold
      Koslow, Susan
      Kostotowski, Andrzeo
      Kraus, Erasmus
      Krause, Rudolf
      Kreismann, Illo
      Kress, R. N.
      Kroeber, A. L.
      Kuntz, Paul G.
      Kusch, Horst
      Kuylen, Krister van
    - Kaftal - Kahane, 1941-1963 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
      Kaftal, George
      Kahane, Henry R.
      Kahane, Penuel P.
    - Kahr, Madlyn, 1962-1967 (Box 6, Reel 2114-2115)
    - Kaiser - Kalinowski, 1955-1965 (Box 6, Reel 2115-2116)
      Kaiser, Walter
      Kalinowski, Lech
    - Kantorwicz, E. H., 1951-1963, undated (Box 6, Reel 2115-2116)
    - Kapp - Kasack, 1941-1965 (Box 6, Reel 2115-2116)
      Kapp, Ernest
      Kapp, Ida
      Karl, Adolph
      Karling, Sten
      Kasack, Hermann
    - Katzenellenbogen, Adolf, 1931-1966, (2 folders) (Box 7, Reel 2116)
    - Kauffmann, Hans, 1953-1967 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
    - Kaufmann, Emil, 1942-1953 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
    - Kaufmann, Georg, 1960-1966 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
    - Kellam - Kelleher, 1952-1970 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
      Kellam, Jack
      Kelleher, Patrick J.
    - Kennan - Kienitz, 1952-1970 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
      Kennan, George F.
      Kessler, Clemencia Hand
      Kienitz, John F.
    - Kimball, Fiske, 1941-1955 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
    - King - Kisch, 1946-1960 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
      King, Edward L.
      King, L.G.T.
      Kisch, Guido
    - Kitzinger - Klauser, 1955-1967 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
      Kitzinger, Ernst
      Klauser, Theodor
    - Klein, Robert, 1957-1966 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
    - Klesse - Koch, 1948-1967 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
      Klesse, Brigitte
      Klessmann, Rüdiger
      Klibansky, Raymond
      Knapp-Fisher, J. S.
      Koch, Rev. Alfred
    - Koch, Robert Alan, 1949-1968 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
    - Koehler - Köhler, 1938-1963 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
      Koehler, Wilhelm and Margarete, 1942-1959
      Koepplin, Dieter, 1963
      Köhler, Wolfgang, 1938-1961
    - Kossoff - Koyré, 1952-1963, undated (Box 7, Reel 2116)
      Kossoff, Florence S.
      Koyré, Alexandre
    - Kracauer - Kraft, 1941-1966 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
      Kracauer, Siegfried
      Kraft, Konrad
    - Krautheimer, Richard, 1938-1967, (2 folders) (Box 7, Reel 2116)
    - Krönig, Wolfgang, 1950-1958 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
    - Kristeller, Paul Oskar, 1947-1976, undated (Box 7, Reel 2116)
    - Kubler, George, 1936-1962 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
    - Kuhn - Kultermann, 1939-1968 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
      Kuhn, Charles L.
      Kultermann, Udo
    - Künstsler - Kurz, 1953-1967 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
      Künstsler, Gustav
      Kupferberg, C. A.
      Kurz, Otto
    - Ladenburg - Lynes (single letters), 1929-1967 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
      Ladenberg, Mrs. Rudolf
      Ladendorf, Heinz
      Laging, Duard W.
      La Marre, John
      Lambert, Phyllis B.
      Landan, Julie
      Lantham, Richard
      Laporte, Paul M.
      Lapp, John C.
      Latte, K.
      Laufer, June
      Laurier, Mrs. Jacques De
      Lawall, David E.
      Leary, Eleanor W.
      Lehmann, Paul
      Lennon, William
      Leonhardt, Leo
      Lering, Antoine
      Lesley, Everett P., Jr.
      Lexow, Jan Hendrick
      Leynen, Hilde
      Leyritz, Gabariel Chaneaux de
      Li, Chu-tsing
      Linardos, Ilialna
      Lilienfeld, Karl
      Lincoln, Carolyn R.
      Lindroth, Sten
      Lindsay, Kenneth C.
      Lisco, Karen
      Lissim, Simon
      Lowey, Alice
      London News
      Loomis, Roger S.
      Lowry, Bates
      Lucas, S.
      Luce, Robert
      Ludden, Franklin Monroe
      Lumb, E. Sue
      Lyon, Quinter M.
      Lynes, Mildred C. (Mrs. Russell Lynes)
    - Lachmann, Claire, 1957-1961 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
    - Ladner, Gerhard B., 1952-1975 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
    - Lafond - Lankheit, 1942-1966 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
      Lafond, Jean
      Lamarre, John H.
      Lambert, Phyllis
      Lanckorónska, Countess Maria
      Landsberger, Franz
      Lang, Renée B.
      Langer, William L.
      Lankheit, Klaus
    - Larrabee - Laurvik, 1940-1951 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
      Larrabee, Harold A.
      Larrabee, Stephen A.
      Laurvik, J. N.
    - Lauts - Lavalleye, 1950-1972 (Box 7, Reel 2116)
      Lauts, Jan
      Lavalleye, Jan
    - Lavin, Irving and Marilyn, 1950-1966 (Box 7, Reel 2116-2117)
    - Lawrence - Lee, 1936-1966, undated (Box 7, Reel 2116-2117)
      Lawrence, Marion
      Lawrence, Sidney
      Leadbeatter, Dorothy
      Leake, Chauncey D.
      Lederer, Wolfgang
      Lee, Paul A.
    - Lee, Rensselaer Wright, 1938-1967, undated (Box 7, Reel 2116-2117)
    - Leeper - Lehman, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Reel 2116-2117)
      Leeper, John
      Lehman, Robert
    - Lehmann, Karl, 1927-1959 (Box 7, Reel 2116-2117)
    - Lehman, Phyllis W., 1947-1965 (Box 7, Reel 2116-2117)
    - Lehman - Leroquais, 1940-1965 (Box 7, Reel 2116-2117)
      Lehamnn-Haupt, Hellmut
      Lejeune, Jean
      Lenneberg, Edith
      Lerici, Carlo M.
      Leroquais, Victor
    - Levey - Levin, 1949-1968 (Box 7, Reel 2116-2117)
      Levey, Michael
      Levin, Harry T.
    - Lewine, Milton J., 1964-1965 (Box 7, Reel 2116-2117)
    - Lewis, Wilmarth S., 1959-1966 (Box 7, Reel 2116-2117)
    - Liebeschütz - Loomis, 1953-1965 (Box 8, Reel 2117)
      Liebeschütz, Hans
      Lieftnick, G. I.
      Linder, Harold F.
      Loeschcke, Walter
      Lohamm-Siems, Isa
      Loomis, Laura H.
    - Lopez - Lossky, 1950-1967 (Box 8, Reel 2117)
      Lopez, Robert S.
      Lord, Eileen A.
      Lord, L. E.
      Loshak, David
      Lossky, Boris
    - Lotz, Wolfgang, 1954-1964 (Box 8, Reel 2117)
    - Lowe, E. A., 1940-1959 (Box 8, Reel 2117)
    - Lowinsky, Edward E., 1943-1967, (4 folders) (Box 8, Reel 2117)
    - Ludwig - Lyna, 1947-1959, undated (Box 8, Reel 2117)
      Ludwig, Allan
      Lyna, Frederic, undated
    - Mc/Mac, General (single letters, McCarthy - McNulty [Mc and Mac interfiled]), 1941-1966 (Box 8, Reel 2117)
      McCarthy, Joseph L.
      McElhinney, Alice L.
      MacGreevy, Thomas
      McKinnis, Fred L.
      MacLagan, Eric
      McNamee, Father Maurice
      McNulty, J. Bard
    - McCall, John E., 1939-1941 (Box 8, Reel 2117)
    - McCormick, Thomas J., Jr., circa 1951-1966, (2 folders) (Box 8, Reel 2117)
    - MacCracken - McMahon, 1944-1966 (Box 8, Reel 2117)
      MacCracken, R. A.
      McGee, Anne
      McGrath, Robert L.
      McGuire, William
      McKechwie, Margaret
      McKenzie, A. Dean
      McKibbin, David
      McMahon, A. Phillip
    - M, General (single letters, Magallón - Mylonas), 1932-1968, (2 folders) (Box 8, Reel 2117)
      Magallón, Don Tomás
      Magnuson, Torgil
      Malkiel, Jakow
      Maltese, Corrado
      Mandelbaum, Maruice
      Mango, Cyril
      Maniates, Maria Rika
      Manuel, Fritzie
      Mar, André de la
      Marabottini, Alessandrom
      Marazza, Achille
      Marchand, Hans
      Marck, Jan H. M. van der
      Marg, W.
      Marichal, Robert
      Markham, Anne
      Marks, Peter
      Marrow, James
      Martens, Bela
      Martin, William E.
      Martin, Y.
      Martone, Father Thomas
      Marruach, Acisclo
      Masi, Alessandro de
      Mattingly, J. R.